Most AI tutors forget you when the conversation ends.
In every new session, you have to repeat your goals and preferences.
WeakSpot is different. It is an English coach with persistent memory
that learns what works for each learner across sessions.
Here, I only submit a short piece of writing.
Qwen diagnoses the language and identifies durable information.
In the same structured response,
it proposes durable memory candidates.
WeakSpot stores my communication goal, concise-feedback preference,
and evidenced grammar weaknesses.
No separate memory workflow
or additional model call is required.
In a new session, WeakSpot does not send
the learner's entire history back to the model.
Qwen text-embedding-v4 and lexical matching
retrieve the most relevant memories.
The final Memory Pack contains no more than six memories
and must fit inside a 700-token budget.
This is not an append-only transcript.
Equivalent observations are merged instead of duplicated.
Conflicting evidence replaces the active fact,
and the previous version is archived as superseded.
The learner can inspect, correct, pin,
or forget any memory.
Every graded attempt updates strategy evidence
for a specific skill and exercise format.
WeakSpot combines mastery gap, error density, spacing,
historical performance, productive difficulty, and exploration.
The recommendation explains why it was selected
and links back to the supporting memories.
The FastAPI backend runs in Docker on Alibaba Cloud ECS.
Qwen 3.7 Max handles deep analysis and planning.
Qwen 3.7 Plus handles faster workflows,
and text-embedding-v4 powers the hybrid memory ranker.
DynamoDB stores cross-session memory,
lifecycle metadata, and auditable recall traces.
The benchmark reaches 100% Recall at Six,
respects every token budget, and reduces context by 82.6%.
WeakSpot remembers not only your mistakes,
but your goals and how you learn best.